Every single week, I come online
and I critique strangers on the internet
to look
at their landing pages, their content,
to see where the bottleneck is for them to
make more sales. Why the glasses? Well,
last week I had an outlier video.
It performed better than all my other
videos. I'll show you.
For some reason,
it's just doing really well.
Average view duration, five minutes.
The views are just absolutely the best
performer in the last 28 days.
Declan,
this is your opportunity to get some
screen grabs.
And do you know what, Declan?
You can even keep in the footage of me
telling you to
get the screen grabs.
And the reason we're doing screen grabs,
people, is because I
think I was guilty of trying to make my
thumbnails look too much like good
thumbnails,
and they could be a little bit disjointed
from the video that people
get. And I don't want that emotion
when they start watching a video.
I want them to think,
"Look at this prat in yellow tint glasses
and a gray jumper
in front of a beautiful car
that some people will think
is a green screen
backdrop." When they click the video,
that's what they get.
Now, before we get into Dave's Doors,
there's a link in the
description, and if you click on that,
you give me your email address and your
bloody website, I get in,
I do all of this, and I give you some free
advice. Beneath that,
if you're not interested in having a
critique, I've got
what has been a game changer for a lot of
businesses.
If you've got a website
or landing page and you want to increase
your conversions,
you can have that for free.
And beneath that,
there'll be the $99 content creation
course that helps people make content.
But James, stop promoting your stuff.
Let's get into it. We've got Dave's Doors.
We're starting right from the beginning.
I'll also put a link in. Today
is the 26th of June.
For the next couple of days on TikTok
Shop,
there's nearly a third off all Nutonic
products. And TikTok pay for that, not us.
I had to put these glasses on because I'm
old. Actually, no, let's keep them off.
For sex appeal and for the clips that
are going on social media.
Okay, Dave's Doors.
I never in a million years thought I'd be
getting excited about
arriving on a page that promotes doors.
But you know what?
This is one of those things, brother.
Until I saw your page,
I hadn't even thought about the fact
that my front door
is fully customizable.
I've never looked at my house and gone,
"Is that the door I
want? Is that the door
that I deserve?" And now you've got me
questioning
everything. Fantastic. What a niche.
I'm so happy you're here.
I will bring my own personal anecdote into
this.
The first day I moved into my house,
I got rid of the lock and put a
keypad entry. At university,
hated having to carry a key.
I've just always never liked the idea
that if you lose a bit of metal, you lose
access to your house. So now,
keypad for the front door,
never got to worry.
My cleaners got their own keypad for the
front door.
Anyone needs to come around,
you've got a keypad.
And the smart thing is, if someone
was to give that keypad number to a
robber,
I can look at the system,
see what code you used,
and see who gave away the code.
Back to Dave and his doors. Wow.
Love this.
I reckon I'm only maybe two
or three pieces of content away from
thinking, "Dave,
we need new doors.
We need a new front door." I think we
could already be there.
Nationwide UK delivery door suppliers
and installers.
Now we can see here, these reels
are non-existent.
If I was you, this is the best thing
that I can tell you, Dave,
you need to start
posting some reels because even though the
pictures are great and I get a lot
from this, we miss one thing, and that
is transformative process.
Okay, and this, no, no.
That YouTube Shorts thing, no, no, no.
Everything is a story.
Let's imagine this gym, for instance.
This is an empty room.
It's an industrial space. I record that.
Then bit by bit, there's gym equipment,
there's flooring, there's a desk, there's
lighting. Soon over time,
it turns into what is the ultimate lab
pad. Sauna, car,
building a studio upstairs. This
is a story.
And when people look at your story,
they think about themselves.
So again,
when any personal trainer talks about
weight loss, the person doesn't
care that someone from Nottingham lost 30
kilograms.
But if they can understand
and become involved in the story,
they can think of
themselves losing that weight.
Same way with bathroom renovations.
If you show someone some amazing bathroom
renovation, they don't really care that a
bathroom in Northumbria looks better.
They're thinking about their own bathroom.
They're becoming inspired.
Whether it's the weight loss,
whether it's the
transformation of the bathroom in here.
Even looking at your page,
I'm going through that right now.
And if you were to show me what a door
looked like before and then afterwards,
we're getting that transformative before
and after.
We're telling a story,
even in a 10-second reel.
There doesn't need to be a hook, a setup,
a payoff.
You're in a beautiful business where you
can go, "Here's a door that before was
naff.
Now here's a beautiful one." I want to
know about functions, features,
snazzy locks,
because right now you're just showing me
the after, not the
before.
And I guarantee almost all of your
customers, take away new builds,
they're going to have an old door.
So let's show the before, show the
after. Every single bit of work
that you've done is a story that you
can tell.
And people will follow you because they'll
find it pleasant.
I follow Terry the Tiler.
Do you know what I've never done in my
life? Tiled.
But brother, in bed,
I'm just watching this.
It's transformative. It's a story.
I even got into a wormhole last night.
There's these guys...
I think you can actually...
Don't tell James. Show.
On TikTok,
I think you can see what things you've
liked.
Oh, James, you bastard.
You didn't show love.
There are people
that come to a driveway
and they get this black stuff and
sweep it around. I was hooked. I
was watching that for ages.
I'm like,
"I should be going to bed." I had a call
at 6:30 AM, but I'm there
watching this guy go around doing
driveways.
And it was transformative because the
driveway before looked crap.
Then afterwards,
the driveway looked amazing.
It's transformative.
Anytime you can intertwine a story like
this.
Mate,
I'm excited for you because you're not
tapping into this.
Reels are the best place to do this
because video is going to be the best
place.
And it doesn't even matter how good you
are with technology.
You arrive at the scene,
you're about to do your work,
you record the door, you
maybe go up and get the handle,
a little bit of ASMR,
which I think means the
noise.
Then maybe a little bit of the story of
fitting it.
Maybe there is conflict, dilemma.
Maybe the door doesn't fit.
Maybe it needs to be sanded.
Maybe the first time you go to close the
door, it's a
little bit off,
so you have to very carefully do your
thing to sand the side of it
so it fits.
Because we love to see conflict.
We love to see people overcome this kind
of stuff because then again, it shows us
that not all door installations
are perfect, but you have the skill set
necessary.
Maybe I should get into the door business.
You have the skill set necessary to make
it work.
And by overcoming those challenges,
you're showing us your competency.
Now, I want to know about styles.
I want to know about colors.
I want to know about weather
and how that's going to impact it.
This is great, mate. This
is such an opportunity.
I don't know anyone...
And Dave's Doors, I like it. Alliteration.
Fantastic. Now we get to your website.
Let's have a little look. And it
is a generic website, which is fine.
Design your very own bespoke composite
door. Going to throw it out there.
Don't know what composite means.
Either I'm an idiot
or you're talking in your
terminologies. A bit like accountants say,
"And the revenue." I go, "Who's
that?" They go, "HMRC." I'm like, "Well,
why didn't you just call it HMRC?
Because you lost me the moment you said
revenue." A bit like when PTs go,
"And just
stop eating carbohydrates." You're like,
"Well, what's a carbohydrate?" They're
like, "Mate, carbohydrates." You're like,
"Mate
So we're talking fruit,
we're talking bread, we're talking pasta,
we're talking
potato.
Are we talking broccoli as carbohydrates?
Oh, but no,
technically we're talking about starches
and sugar.
People talk in their own languages.
Again,
I went to look at getting a customized
exhaust on the GT3.
Someone's like, "Yeah, mate,
so we could do a cat delete,
or we could do a straight
pipe,
or we could just put a titanium muffler
on.
What do you want?" I go, "Mate,
I don't understand what you're saying.
You might as well be speaking German."
Talking German, that's an interesting one.
They say, "I love you," they're like,
"Ich liebe dich." You're like, "Whoa,
fucking
come on, mate,
I fucking love you." So yeah, what
is a composite door?
Would this be better if said,
"Design your very own bespoke door?"
Probably,
because I'm like,
is composite what I need?
Do I need a carbon composite fucking
ceramic door?
Do I need that? Same with cars, right?
We did the PPF video yesterday.
People are like, "Yeah, mate,
just had a ceramic coating." What's a
ceramic coat?
What? I don't know what that is, brother.
"Well, you know, ceramic coating."
That doesn't help.
"Yeah, we just put the PPF on it, yeah,
and then we do a vinyl.
Then we..." Just talk to me like I'm an
idiot. What's a nootropic?
Supplements that help you think
and concentrate in stressful times.
Sound, because we do it as well.
We say nootropics.
Do you know what,
this whole video could just be Dave's
doors.
I'm going to limit myself, though.
We got 16 minutes on the memory card.
Internal doors, hardwood doors. Mate,
this is one of them things, right?
That excites me because you put a wrap on
a car, it feels like a brand-new car.
You put a new door in a house,
you got a brand-new house.
Not quite, but you know what I mean.
Doing interiors, let's change the doors,
babe.
Let's change the door.
I'm inspired to fucking go door shopping.
I love this, mate. Because the thing is,
you get these transformative processes on
social media, you spark the curiosity.
And with a bathroom renovation,
you've got to pull stuff out,
get the tiles out.
There's going to be plumbing.
What happens if the hot water stops coming
out?
What if there's a leak? There's always...
With a door, it's easy.
You're just taking a wooden thing off the
latches. I'm excited, mate.
This looks fucking cool.
So your website's sick.
Your offering's sick.
The whole thing that's going on here,
I'm buzzing
about. Your socials are poo, and this
is great.
This is opportunity. What's this?
Click on your link. What we got here?
Review and win John Lewis voucher. No,
mate. Mate, you want to... No.
How about this?
Just get loads of jobs to get review...
Why is that your link, brother? Why?
That should be just a link to the flipping
website, bro.
And also, when you're fitting a job,
maybe just say, "I'll give you a
5% discount if you give us a positive
review when we're finished." Then just
increase your prices by 5% across the
board and just do that.
Then you charge the same,
you get the same,
and everyone feels compelled to give
you that. Mate, what an opportunity.
Let's just get this right.
Let's start putting out content.
128 posts. Missed opportunity.
Every single job,
every single person you send to a job, oh,
and a little video or
a picture before and after.
Video's going to do better because Reels
are what get
pushed to people. You ever notice
that when people go into bed at night
and they
just are brain dead,
that's where it's going to come up,
and you're going to motivate people to get
doors. Dave, I'm excited for you.
The content creation course that's $99
that's
in my description here could be perfect
for you.
Okay,
we've got to do a little bit of fitness
stuff. Mano Egleen.
Okay, hate your picture.
When I see you doing this,
I just think all
he cares about is himself.
"I help busy men get ripped with
intermittent fasting in
90 days." I'd rather you just said,
"In 90 days," and then I wish I could find
out
more about your system with intermittent
fasting.
"Dream body with only three hours a week
and daily dessert.
DM me 'cut' or reply 'here.'" Let's see
what happens there, shall we?
Nothing happens. Nothing happens, brother.
This is stupid. What's the point, mate?
What is the point?
Go to ManyChat, set up an automation.
The fucking...
It's not hard, brother. Then
that DM could've been sent.
You're pissing me off, mate. Honestly,
such a low-level thing to do.
Okay, let's click on your website.
Fucking sign-up form.
"Lose that skinny fat look." What
if they're not skinny fat?
"Get in the best shape of your life." Do
you know how many fucking personal
trainers say,
"Get in the best shape of your life?" Be
different, bro.
"Enquire today and start
that journey." Huh? Goo? Can't say that.
Bruv, I want to know how much it is,
what I get, why I need it,
why I should trust
you.
That is the imperative key components of a
landing page.
So you, bro, download
that for free in the description because
if you
send someone to this, they
are more likely to buy it than
if you send them to this.
I would ask how many people you're getting
applying, but I already know, not a lot,
bro. Come on, change that up.
Because by the looks of it, you're not
that much of a physique bro.
Your videos that perform best
are you talking.
Like high protein ice cream.
Double down on this, bro. Ugh, brother.
What's that, brother? Ugh, brother, ugh.
You're gone, bro. Next,
we've got Scotty2Hotty.
Now,
I'm excited to do this one because I know
Scotty is already in the mentorship.
I've been through some of this stuff Do
you know what, mate?
I'm going to throw it out there.
I like this.
It's got to go, because 10K, Scotty Massa,
not to be
confused with Massapus. Sorry,
any South Africans watching.
You're the brand, bro. This guy here,
you're the brand brother. Okay?
You're the brand.
So let's get Scotty2Hottie up in here.
Now, let's get rid of maybe some of this.
If you got rid of this, think higher,
feel deeper, it's a little bit, you know.
Then we wouldn't have this above the fold
here because it just says hit.
If we got rid of that
and you put hit the contact button to
inquire, and you put
that there, where is the contact button?
Message? DM? How to book?
Let's clean that up a bit.
That call to action just needs a little
bit of help.
I want you here. Let's go to your reels.
Now, these look, do okay.
They do okay.
Let's watch some of them, shall we?
I'm going to say a similar kind of thing.
I'm not seeing any transformative
processes.
I would love to see blank canvas,
the body, the flesh,
person, their conflict, which it could be,
"I've always wanted to get a
tattoo. I've always been too scared.
I've always wanted to do this for this
reason.
I've lost someone dear to me.
There's something that's really important
to me.
This date is really important to me.
My dad died a couple years ago." Then the
transformative process, the tattoo, the
meaning, the impact,
what it meant to them,
why they've been waiting.
And I would love to see some more of that,
because then again, people can go, "Wow,
that person has a date that's really
important to them.
I have a date that's really important to
me.
That person got that tattoo on their arm,
and although I love it, I would like to
get it on my leg." Maybe someone
celebrating the birthdate of their
firstborn child, something like that.
Let's get some stories in here.
This is Sandra.
She's petrified of needles.
She made the trip over to Malta.
And again, this is the other thing, right?
Am I right in thinking, Scotty,
that you are in Malta?
Oh, yes. Let me tell you this, bro, okay?
And you may not have realized this before.
You're in Malta.
That's one of the coolest places in
Europe, bro. It's undiscovered.
Everyone wants to go to Malta. Everyone.
So let's make this a part of the brand,
because do you know what?
I don't want to go to Scunthorpe to get a
tattoo.
I don't want to go to Solihull to get a
I don't even want to go to Solihull.
I don't want to go to London.
I don't want to get stuck in traffic.
You know when people go to Turkey to get a
hair transplant, it's not just that
they're going to Turkey to get a hair
transplant.
It's that they're going to Turkey
and they're getting a hair transplant.
You need to be partnering
and talking to travel agents,
working with a hotel.
They get picked up with a minibus.
They get taken to the hotel.
They come in for a tattoo.
You give them a guarantee that,
do you know what?
If you hate it, come back to Malta.
I'm pretty sure you told me in the Discord
that
you have a family member
that does tattoo removal.
Let's throw that guarantee in there,
and let's look at the stats of how many
people
actually get removal,
because I don't think it's that many.
Let's turn this into a holiday.
Let's turn it into an experience.
Let's turn this into a bundle trip of a
lifetime.
Let's get people excited, because
that person might go, "Hey,
I'm going to Malta to
get this work done." You might even then
have an incentive, bring a friend.
Friends retreat, you get picked up,
we put you up in a hotel.
Now, unfortunately,
we don't like tattooing people that
are hungover, so we're
going to give you Tuesday, Wednesday,
Thursday for the tattoo.
Friday night,
we'll reserve a table at our favorite
restaurant.
You guys will go out.
There's going to be some free sangria on
the house as part of
the tattoo process. Make it fun.
Make it big. This is sick, bro.
Again, you're already well-established.
You're already well-known by the looks of
it. Let's make Malta part of this brand.
I'm sure that the Maltese government
and tourism might even have some fun with
this. The reason
that I'm so excited about this is
that let's make it a part of
the experience. So it's going to go,
if I type in Malta here, what do
we get? Beautiful. Oh, look at this.
Show me a reel. Give me a reel, brother.
Give me a reel. Oh, stop giving me reels.
That's boring.
Footage, water, beach, visit Malta,
Europe's best
tattoo. Talk to me about the package.
Sell me the holiday,
because this isn't just a tattoo, bro.
This is an experience.
I think I want to hear a bit more of your
voice, even though
you are Scottish.
I've not really said
that to many Scottish people.
Here today,
we're with a client that's doing...
Tell me. Give me context.
Because at the moment,
I'm just watching someone get a tattoo.
I don't want to just do that.
I want to be involved.
What we're doing here is this.
It took me seven years to become this
precise. And then do you know what?
I would love to see some banter where
maybe including pop culture.
Let's say Liver King just went on a mad
one yesterday.
You should, for banter, get
that picture of Liver King looking like
he's having a
psychotic episode.
Put it on someone's calf,
and then peel off as if you're about
to start tattooing,
and then people will be like, "No way,
ooh." And then you're
like, "We're just joking. By the way,
if you want to come to visit Malta, DM the
word Malta,
and we'll send you our tourism package
bundle." You know what I mean?
Let's have some fun with this.
Let's get some views.
Capture me in the first five to 10
seconds, because guess what, bro?
There are loads of people out there
that want a tattoo.
that want to visit Malta.
You get to combine the two.
I think there's such opportunity here as
well.
You can tell because I'm excited by it.
Now,
let's just quickly have a look at the
website one more time.
Fill out the form below.
We'll get back to you shortly by email.
Again, maybe something like this,
connect it with a travel agent.
What month do you want to come?
How many there are of you?
What kind of tattoo procedure do you want?
We'll float you the cost of the tattoo,
a bundle package, how much it'll cost for
flights, accommodation, whatever it is.
Because some people just don't want to
deal with all that stuff.
They would rather just have a package
done, dealt with, whatever.
And then with the travel agent as well,
sometimes you and all your mates can pay
what you owe to the travel agents so you
haven't got to chase people for money.
Guys, exciting opportunity. Love it.
Those of you watching,
if at any point you want me to critique
your stuff, don't be
shy, don't be afraid. I will be nice,
unless you have topless bloody profile
pictures. Get stuck in.
Use the link in the description.
Thank you so much for watching.
Those of you that have been patient enough
to watch
this far, if you haven't already,
definitely check out this video,
because maybe it
was the glasses or maybe it
was just how amazing this video was
that got so many
views. You have a good day. Bye-bye.